I'll give birth to you once more.
I'll make sure you'll never die this time.
I'll make sure you'll never
be broken this time.
By sharing my power with you.
Oh, but if I grant it to you all at once,
you might not be able to endure it.
So I'll make it so you're able to take it in
little by little by little.
And to do that...
I'll spread my seeds throughout the world.
Someday your human body will eventually
be able to accept that power.
Then you'll just need to absorb
that power one by one.
Once you've obtained all that power,
then you'll remember everything,
and this time we'll be able
to be live together forever.
Kurumi Tokisaki, I'm grateful to you.
You truly were my wonderful friend
until the very end.
Zaphkiel!
I'm sorry, Kurumi Tokisaki.
Also, thank you.
I'm able to stand before him
once more thanks to you.
How dare you?
Shido, run.
It's been a long time.
We finally meet again, Shin.
Shin?
Have you remembered for me?
Mio!
Wha?!
Kurumi Tokisaki's life signs have vanished.
It looks like she's completely dead.
Wh-What on earth is that?
Reine?
Please, reject my stupid thought
like you always do.
Reine, chastise me like you always do!
Kotori, you really are a smart girl.
MARIA!
I'm grateful, Kotori.
What for?
I owe you one.
You've been protecting Shin all this time,
and I'm truly grateful for that.
Reine, who on earth are you?
I'm sure the answer isn't that far
from what you're already imagining.
That is me, and I am that.
We're one will in two bodies.
There was work I had to do on this end, too.
So it was more convenient to split myself.
Especially when granting everyone Sephirah.
Granting Sephirah?
Then you're Phantom?!
Yes, and I am also the Spirit
of Origin Kurumi mentioned.
Kotori, the time I spent with you was fun.
But that's over now.
What?!
Reine!
Everyone, continue the mission.
We've lost one ally and gained one enemy.
That's all.
Oh? You recovered quickly.
I'm handling control of the ship,
so you could have remained
depressed a little longer.
Hmph.
If you're trying to light a fire under me,
then do a better job of it.
Pardon me then.
It seems I still have room to learn about
the intricacies of the human heart.
Reine?!
It's all right, Shin.
Mio...
Shin, have you remembered for me?
I've missed you for so long.
I wanted to see you for so, so long.
I've lived this long entirely for that feeling.
There's so much I want to share with you.
There's so much
I haven't been able to say to you.
Ahh, but it's okay.
This time, we'll be together forever, Shin.
I'm... happy to see you, too, Mio.
Shin!
I'm sorry I left you alone for so long
and made you feel so lonely.
I truly am sorry I died before you.
Don't be.
It's nothing for you to apologize for—
But...
What is all this?
What on earth have you done
in order to revive me, Shinji Takamiya?
Whatever it took.
I did anything I had to.
I did everything I needed to in order
to see you one more time, Shin.
Shin? Are you okay?
Mio... No.
Huh?
No... You can't do that.
You can't sacrifice others,
no matter what your goal is.
Yeah, you're right.
But then what was I supposed to do?
You were the only one for me.
After losing you,
I had no more reason to live, Shin.
But I'm not weak like humans are.
Even if I wanted to die, I couldn't.
I'm also not strong like humans are.
I couldn't just forget about you either.
So what was I supposed to do?
That's...
I'm sorry, that was mean.
There's no way you could
answer when I ask like that.
But it's okay, Shin.
Leave it to me.
Mio?
Time for the finishing touches.
I'll leave your memories as Shin
and erase all your other memories.
Then you'll be restored to Shin
just as I've been restored to Mio.
Thank you for everything until now, Shido.
Shido!
Tohka!
Sorry I'm late, Shido!
We heard the story over the intercom.
Is that really Reine?
Alert. She's also the Spirit
of Origin and Phantom,
so she's being too greedy.
Shido!
Wait a little bit for me, Shin.
Where did you send Shido?!
Somewhere safe.
That way he won't get caught up in our battle.
Yamabuki?! Why are you here?!
That's our line!
Itsuka, where did you come from?!
Were you clinging to the ceiling
to go after Ai?!
Hey, is Tohka not enough for you?!
That's so lame!
Huh?
Is this the spatial quake shelter?
Why are you stating the obvious?
Now move, you're scaring me!
Yamabuki!
Wh-What is it?!
Which shelter is this?!
Which one?
Obviously it's the one beneath the school.
The school...
I see.
That's a pretty long distance
from where I previously was.
Sorry, everyone, but let me through!
I have to go!
You idiot!
The warning hasn't been lifted yet!
Where do you even plan on going?
I have to go.
To where Tohka and Origami are!
Huh?
Oh, so that's what's up.
I haven't seen them in a while, yeah.
I just thought they were
in a different shelter.
Got her!
H-Hey you four, what are you doing?!
T-Tonomachi!
Yamabuki, Hazakura, Fujibakama!
Hurry up and go!
Those two are still stuck outside, right?
You can thank us for today
with lunch tomorrow!
That's so lame.
Give us a chance to look cool now and then.
Hey, let go of me already!
Sensei, this is a good moment!
What are you all doing, jeez?!
Go a little easier on me, please!
Everyone, thank you!
Hey! You can't do it, Itsuka!
The door won't open
until the warning is lifted!
Michael!
Lataib!
Whoa!
That's so lame.
Mio.
You are Reine, right?
Yeah, that's right, Tohka.
Are you sure you won't reconsider?
You've done a lot for us.
I'd rather not fight you if we don't have to.
I see.
That's a shame.
Hey!
What are you doing ignoring us and
acting like the final battle is starting?!
Seriously, this is outlandish!
Ein Sof Ohr.
Huh?
What's this?
Blossom.
The Bandersnatch squad is wiped out!
Nibeelcole has vanished and can't reform!
Ship 3, Galdrabok, is unable
to maintain its Territory!
It's going down!
So you've finally appeared, Deus!
My beloved Spirit!
I really do feel sorry toward all of you.
That's why I won't tell you not to fight back.
Because that's a natural right you all have.
Now, come at me,
my cute daughters.
Here, here!
Origami, are you all right?!
Hmm, looks like your plan worked.
You're the one who took out Artemisia, yeah?
It surprised me when I saw a key suddenly
thrust in from out of nowhere.
Hmm?
U-Um, uh...
Seeing you this up close,
you really are a normal girl, huh?
Makes me wonder where they got that talk of
enemy lifeforms incapable of communication.
A bombardment?
Origami!
Defensive formation!
You can't! Run!
Huh?
Hey!
Mike!
What's going on? She's dead?
That should be where Master
and the others were fighting!
Let's go!
Captain, please take care
of Mike and the rest.
If you take them to Fraxinus' medical facility,
it might be possible to resuscitate them.
Fraxinus?
The flagship currently fighting DEM.
We're going to aid Shido and the others!
What incredible magic capacity.
Though your attacks are too direct.
I know you're happy
for our long awaited reunion,
but settle down a bit, Ellen.
I see you're still making
yourself look younger.
Well, not that I'm one to talk right now.
Shut up!
Why?!
Why did you betray us, Elliot?!
We had vowed to each other that
we would get our retaliation,
our revenge, our retribution
against all of mankind!
You turned your back on our vows!
You seduced my little sister,
stole the fruits of our research,
and became our enemy!
Know that you will pay
for that sin with your death!
I do feel bad for you and Ike.
Well, I wouldn't say I seduced Karen,
but before I knew it she had
arranged her matters to be at my side.
Regardless, I never wanted to be your enemy.
It's just that the path I chose collided
with the path you two chose in a weird way.
Nonsense!
I still haven't forgotten the resentment
I feel for our village being burned down,
or the hatred I feel for our comrades' murder.
I just...
Have you noticed it, too, Ellen?
This incredible spirit power.
Deus!
Yeah.
There's no mistaking it.
When I first saw that Spirit, I thought,
"Ahh, how pretty."
Then, "Is it okay to sacrifice such an
innocent child for the sake of our revenge?"
I thought, "If we do, then how
are we any different from the humans
who burned down our home?"
You've always been pure and direct.
The most so of all three of us.
So I'm sure we're the two who changed.
But I still consider you
and Ike to be my friends.
That will never change.
I'm sure Karen feels the same way, too.
What are you-?!
If you can't forgive me, then that's fine.
But at least give Karen another chance—
Chastiefol!
Pierce him, Rhongomiant!
Gungnir!
Kaguya, Yuzuru, are you ready?
Wh-Who do you think you're talking to?!
I'm perfectly good to go!
Agreed. No matter how powerful our foe,
a Yamai will never back down.
Good!
Tohka, you won't be able
to defeat me like that.
Yeah, I'm sure I won't.
Raphael!
Yes! El Kanaf!
A splendid surprise attack. However-
Sandalphon!
Halvanhelv!
Kaguya, behind you!
Huh?!
Ah? Huh?
K-Kaguya!
Yuzu...
Kaguya, Kaguya!
Hang in there, Kaguya!
Kaguya! Kaguya!
Please let me make it in time!
What?
What's happening here?!
Now then, Shido Itsuka.
Let's decide here and now
which of us is fit
to obtain the Spirits' power.
Episode 5
Mother Mio
Episode 6 "The Three Magi"
A cruel fate assails
the young Westcott and others.
However, a suspicious smile forms on his lips.
Next episode is Episode 6:
The Three Magi.
This is where it all began.